http://www.techsupportalert.com/privacy-policy.htm

Skip to main content
toggle-button
Main menu
HomeHomepageLoginMy account/Change PWRegisterWindowsDesktop SoftwareWindows AppsPortable AppsWindows 64 bit SoftwareMacLinuxAndroidiOSOnline AppseBooksNewNew ArticlesRecently Updated ArticlesRecent CommentsHighest RatedResourcesNewsTipsTech videosSecurity Guides & ArticlesHow-to Guides & TutorialsBest Download SitesBest Tech Support SitesForumAboutAboutContactFAQContributePrivacy PolicyCondition of Use
toggle-button
toggle-button
This is the Privacy Policy that applies to this site. It explains how we handle personal information and comply with the requirements of the privacy laws. If you have further questions relating to this policy, please contact us.
The term "www.techsupportalert.com" or "us" or "we" refers to the owner of this website. The term "you" refers to the user or viewer of our website.
Collecting information about you
We collect personal information from users who register at our site as well as  subscribers to our RSS feeds. The main types of information we collect are contact details, such as email addresses and names. We collect most of this information directly from individuals when they voluntarily register at our web site or subscribe to our RSS feeds.
We also collect statistical information from site visitors through the Google Analytics web statistics service and standard weblog analysis packages such as AWStats. This information includes details of the browser you use, the operating system you are using and other similar information. Full details can be found on the Google Analytics website and on the AWStats website .  You can disable the collection of this statistical information by turning off JavaScript in your web browser and reconfiguring the privacy settings in your browser though this may create possible navigation problems for you on this site and other sites.
Using and disclosing your personal information
Our purpose in collecting information about you is to deliver the site services you requested such as the ability to post to our forum, make comments under your own user name, receive email notifications  and RSS feeds to which you subscribe and to operate our business efficiently.
This website, email notifications and RSS feeds to which you subscribe may contain advertisements but we will not disclose any personal information you have provided to these advertisers or any other outside parties without your permission except where:
It is required by law;
It is permitted by this Privacy Policy;
It is believed necessary to provide you with goods or services you have requested;
Some or all of the assets and operations of this website and/or RSS feeds are transferred to another party in connection with a merger or sale or change of ownership;
It is necessary to protect the rights, property or personal safety of our employees, our other customers, or any member of the public.
If we collect or use personal information in ways other than as stated in this Privacy Policy, we will do so in accordance with the requirements of the privacy laws.
Unsubscribing
You can unsubscribe from any of our RSS feeds at any time.
Virtually all RSS client software allow you to unsubscribe yourself and we do nothing to prevent or hinder that process.
Every email copy of our RSS feed explains how to unsubscribe. You may also unsubscribe by sending an unsubscribe request that lists each email address receiving unwanted copies of the RSS feed email to editor@techsupportalert.com
Access to your personal information
If at any time you want to know exactly what personal information we hold about you, you are welcome to email us at the email address shown above. We will always attempt to make this information available to you within 14 days.
If at any time you wish to change personal information that we hold about you because it is inaccurate or out-of-date, please contact us at the email address shown above and we will amend this information. If you wish to have your personal information deleted, please contact us and we will take all reasonable steps to delete it, unless we need to keep it for legal, auditing or internal risk reasons.
Cookies
We use cookie technology on our website to provide information and services to website visitors. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record keeping purposes and are an important tool for facilitating online transactions. They are also useful to determine overall traffic patterns through our website.
The cookies used on this site are mostly self-destructing session cookies. These cookies and the information they contain are erased when users exit this website. The only enduring cookies used on this site are those created when users voluntarily elect to have their login details remembered.
Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. If you do not wish to receive any cookies, you may set your browser to refuse cookies, but this may mean you will not be able to take full advantage of the services on the website. In particular you will not be able to login or logout from our website or forums.
Consent
By providing your email address and other personal information, you consent to the use of your personal information, including your email address, in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the privacy laws.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Policy may be reviewed periodically and we reserve the right to change it at any time.  We recommend you periodically check this privacy policy on the website for any possible changes.
This Privacy Policy was last updated on Tuesday, June 21 2011..
Printer-friendly version
toggle-button
Gizmo's Freeware is Recruiting
We are looking for people with skills or interest in the following areas:
Get notified by email of our latest finds:
Get Easy Access to Frequently Used Symbols Not on Your Keyboard
Instantly Add Color to Black and White Photos with Image Colorizer
